<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Havron</title>
    <link>https://havron.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sam Havron</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 20:09:16 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://havron.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>There once was a cat named Posey</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/writing/posey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 20:09:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/writing/posey/</guid>
      <description>There once was a cat named Posey
Her gaze is often quite dozy
A red bug comes to race
She crouches and gives chase
Her pounce turns the red bug rosy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environs</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/environs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 20:58:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/environs/</guid>
      <description>Some of the places that I like and recommend in New York, presented in no particular order (WIP).
browse  McNally Jackson Independent Booksellers. In Nolita (Manhattan), closest to Bowery , Broadway-Lafayette St , or Spring St . Zabar&amp;rsquo;s. On the Upper West Side (Manhattan), closest to 79 St or 81 St - Museum of Natural History .  eat  La Newyorkina. Mexican ice cream. In Greenwich Village (Manhattan), closest to West 4 St - Washington Sq .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description>Publications  Clinical Computer Security for Victims of Intimate Partner Violence. Sam Havron*, Diana Freed*, Rahul Chatterjee, Damon McCoy, Nicola Dell, and Thomas Ristenpart. USENIX Security 2019 (to appear).
 The Spyware Used in Intimate Partner Violence. Rahul Chatterjee, Periwinkle Doerfler, Hadas Orgad, Sam Havron, Jackeline Palmer, Diana Freed, Karen Levy, Nicola Dell, Damon McCoy, and Thomas Ristenpart. IEEE S&amp;amp;P (Oakland) 2018. [Paper PDF]. Media coverage: The New York Times, Vox, Freedom to Tinker (Princeton CITP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Here is a brief biography suitable for use in brochures, advertisements, media, etc. The image on this page should be of sufficient resolution for small printing. My CV/resume is available here, current as of latest commit.
Sam Havron is a PhD student in computer science at Cornell University; he is in residence at Cornell Tech on Roosevelt Island in New York City. He is part of a research team studying computer security and privacy issues in the context of intimate partner violence (IPV).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/home/</guid>
      <description>-- I&amp;rsquo;m a student at Cornell Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m part of a research team studying computer security and privacy issues in the context of intimate partner violence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/license/</guid>
      <description>You can use this page to put a license on the contents of your blog, like so:
 The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright &amp;copy; 2015 Nishanth Shanmughamnishanth.gerrard@gmail.com
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>