<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Havron</title>
    <link>https://havron.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sam Havron</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 10:02:20 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://havron.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility Statement</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/accessibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 10:02:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/accessibility/</guid>
      <description>General https://havron.dev strives to ensure that its contents are accessible to people with disabilities. https://havron.dev has invested a significant amount of resources to help ensure that its website is made easier to use and more accessible for people with disabilities, with the strong belief that every person has the right to live with dignity, equality, comfort and independence. Accessibility on https://havron.dev  https://havron.dev makes available the UserWay Website Accessibility Widget that is powered by a dedicated accessibility server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RRG</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/rrg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 09:20:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/rrg/</guid>
      <description>About: A biweekly meeting for graduate students advised by Tom Ristenpart, and other relevant researchers. Email the organizers if you are interested in presenting.
Time: biweekly on Fridays, 12:00-13:30 EST. Security Seminar is on the other Fridays.
Location: Bloomberg Center 497 (NYC) or Zoom (681-218-454)
Organizers: Sam Havron (havron@cs.cornell.edu) and Nirvan Tyagi (tyagi@cs.cornell.edu)
Discussion: Join #rrg on our slack (email organizers for an invitation). PIN for Zoom also on slack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/press/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 13:17:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/press/press/</guid>
      <description>Outlets my research has been covered in include: The New York Times, MIT Technology Review, WIRED, NPR (WBUR), The Brooklyn Daily Eagle, Vice, Malwarebytes, Vox, Slate, Smart Cities Dive, Technology Review (Deutschland), Cornell Tech Press Room, and The Cornell Chronicle.
Notable people my research has received public attention from include: U.S. Senator Kamala Harris (D-CA).
On security &amp;amp; privacy in the context of intimate partner violence:
  Our work is discussed in &amp;ldquo;For domestic violence victims, cyberstalking is a growing issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There once was a cat named Posey</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/writing/posey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 20:09:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/writing/posey/</guid>
      <description>There once was a cat named Posey
Her gaze is often quite dozy
A red bug comes to race
She crouches and gives chase
Her pounce turns the red bug rosy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environs</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/environs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 20:58:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/environs/</guid>
      <description>Here is my reading list and a selection of places I recommend in New York. All ordering is arbitrary.
in New York City browse  McNally Jackson Independent Booksellers. In Nolita (Manhattan), closest to Bowery , Broadway-Lafayette St , or Spring St . Zabar&#39;s. On the Upper West Side (Manhattan), closest to 79 St or 81 St - Museum of Natural History .  eat  La Newyorkina. Mexican ice cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/research/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/research/research/</guid>
      <description>Current research collaborators (faculty) include: Tom Ristenpart, Nicki Dell, Rahul Chatterjee, and Damon McCoy.
Awards  Facebook Fellowship Program Finalist 2020  Top 4% of Applicants (1800+ applied)   NortonLifeLock Graduate Research Fellowship Finalist 2020 Advocate of New York City Award. 2019 Best Paper Honorable Mention for [3] at ACM CSCW. November 2019 Cornell Graduate School Fellowship. Top 20% of Cornell doctoral students. August 2017 Louis T. Rader Award for Outstanding Undergraduate Education at the University of Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/bio/</guid>
      <description>Bio for talks+press Here is a brief biography suitable for use in talk announcements, press, etc; this high-resolution image of me should be sufficient for small printing.
Sam Havron is a PhD candidate in computer science at Cornell University; he is in residence at Cornell Tech on Roosevelt Island in New York City. He is part of a research team studying computer security and privacy issues in the context of intimate partner violence (IPV), and he helps lead the first computer security clinic for IPV survivors, in NYC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/home/</guid>
      <description>-- I&#39;m a PhD candidate at Cornell Tech. I&#39;m part of a research team studying computer security and privacy issues in the context of intimate partner violence (IPV), and I help lead the first computer security clinic for IPV survivors, in New York City. Here&#39;s a bio for talks+press.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/license/</guid>
      <description>You can use this page to put a license on the contents of your blog, like so:
 The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright (c) 2015 Nishanth Shanmughamnishanth.gerrard@gmail.com
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>