<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>11 on sam havron</title>
    <link>https://havron.dev/2016/11/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 11 on sam havron</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sam Havron</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 17:19:34 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://havron.dev/2016/11/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>e-mail</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/email/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 17:19:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/email/</guid>
      <description>Use any of these to contact me: sgh65@cornell.edu
havron@cs.cornell.edu
sam@havron.xyz
s@m.havron.xyz (domain hack)
Shouldn&amp;rsquo;t I be obfuscating my above addresses in some fashion? My addresses are easily harvested; for now, I allow this because I want to build a better understanding of the detriments of obfuscation strategies to user-friendliness (including JS environment assumptions) before committing to deploying one. The ultimate necessity of obfuscation is also unclear to me.
Most harvesters use sophisticated regex (and in the case of addresses embedded in images, OCR) techniques to reconstruct e-mail addresses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bio&#43;cv</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 17:48:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/bio/</guid>
      <description>Here is a brief biography suitable for use in brochures, advertisements, media, etc. The image on this page should be of sufficient resolution for small printing. My CV/resume is available on GitHub as a PDF, current as of latest commit.
copy/paste this blurb for talks, etc Sam Havron is a PhD student in computer science at Cornell University; he is in residence at Cornell Tech on Roosevelt Island in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>subdomains</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/subdomains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/subdomains/</guid>
      <description>One of the more compelling reasons to manage a personal domain rather than depending on /~academic/ webpages is the ability to easily create subdomains and link them to dynamic and static backend servers, RESTful lambda gateways, and so forth. All of my publicly-exposed subdomains are as follows; no need to run that hacky dig/nmap/superstarred  script&amp;hellip;
Subdomains currently maintained   havron.xyz; home of my personal webpages. It&amp;rsquo;s hosted on static S3 buckets and the CloudFront CDN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trivia</title>
      <link>https://havron.dev/trivia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://havron.dev/trivia/</guid>
      <description>Grand Staircase in the Tata Innovation Center &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;ask me about&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;   The NUMTOT subculture
  IoT pros and cons 
  Vegetarianism 
  Left-handedness 
  Design flaws. 
  The time I marched in the Macy&amp;rsquo;s Thanksgiving Day Parade in NYC with the Cavalier Marching Band
local attractions in Ithaca, NY adventure   Beebe Lake. Great for running! 
foods   Aladdin&amp;rsquo;s</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>